Courage on high.
Lancaster Skies is a drama, war, action film directed by Callum Burn.
Douglas, a broken, solitary, Spitfire Ace, must overcome his past to lead a
Lancaster bomber crew in the pivotal aerial war over Berlin, in 1944.
Charlie Moore, played by Kris Saddler.
Jo, played by Rosa Coduri-Fulford.
Douglas Miller, played by Jeffrey Mundell.
Thomas Mayfield, played by Vin Hawke.
Alfie Hammond, played by Tom Gordon.
Kate Hedges, played by Joanne Gale.
Lancaster Skies is a 2019 British war film focusing on the
British bomber campaign in World War II.
It is a homage to the British war films of the 1940s and 1950s.
The film explores themes of berlin, germany, world war ii, based
on true story, bomber pilot, royal air force.
The tone is emotional.